Kouban
Private
High
School
People of the drama club!
I want to offer my sincere thanks for your
cooperation in the production my short film.
I want you to know I've already
gotten permission from the school,
so you don't need to worry.
I didn't expect to end up back here.
Senpai, the uniform looks good on you.
Well, it's still embarrassing!
It comes with having a starring role.
That's because you helped
Tsuu-chan with the script, right?
How did I end up as an actor?
I mean...
He wanted to enter this, so...
Short Stories
About Falling In Love
Now accepting submissions!
H-Hang on.
Is this story based on your personal experience?
Is it the story of
the day you fell in love?!
I see, I see!
It's not that! It's totally different!
And, Rin, have you been
acting kinda formal again?
Well, I mean... we're not going
out just yet in the story...
It's kind of like getting into the role.
Oh, I see.
Well, I'm counting on you
for acting advice, then, Nanakura.
Man, feels kind of like
we've gone back to the past!
It really does, Senpai!
Much Ado
About Nothing
X
What exactly were we doing
two years ago, anyway?
Come to think of it, there was
that time you were wearing
that embarrassing costume
and got called to the staff office!
But that never happened.
Stop making stories up!
And then there was the time I won
a hundred mill at the lottery
and then Imp-chan and Spoiled-chan
got me to spend it all on them!
More lies!
Anything come to mind, Nanakura-san?
I wanna do the time an unfinished set
collapsed and you shielded me from it as it fell!
Right now!
We were talking about stuff
from the past, though...
And then you said, "I would never let
an actor get hurt by a set I built!"
That sounds a little cool for me!
Come on, do it, do it, do it!
Y'know, I don't remember you
always being this selfish—
Whoa, Nanakura, look out!
Clatter clash crash!
Senpai... you shielded me—
Yeah.
I would never let an actor
get hurt by a set I built.
You keep laughing!
I've fallen for you!
This is all fake!
What an amazing set!
It's hard to believe
that weird senpai built this...
Hey, it's the newbie.
How's rehearsal going?
No matter how many times I check
my lines, I still get anxious...
Wanna cheat, then?
Which lines have got you nervous?
Well... this part here.
Let's take a look.
Are you making cue cards?
And we're gonna hide them all over the set.
I don't know if that's a good idea...
Which is why we'll keep it a secret.
Um... the handwriting is...
I can't exactly make it out.
I think I'll keep practicing
so I don't have to resort to this!
I'll rehearse until I'm confident!
Sounds good!
Then you won't need a cheap...
uh, a ch-cheat in the—
And cut!
Someone fumbled his line,
so we're starting over!
I'm sowwy!
Good day, ladies and gentleman.
I am the head chef at Arcobaleno,
and my name is Hotta.
Today, I'm going to show you all
how Arcobaleno style acqua pazza is made.
First, let's have my apprentice
introduce our ingredients.
Huh, where did she go?
It's almost my turn.
Did Senpai put this up?
I told him I didn't need cue cards...
Enjoy your stage debut!
He's so silly.
Apprentice, what were you doing there?
Oh, nothing much!
I think I'll be okay.
Pretty slick, Kitahama-senpai-kun.
Stop it!
I mean, the whole reason I wrote
that note was to help her not stress out...
It's occurring to me that this film
might be totally embarrassing for me!
Okay, scene 15 next. Everybody ready?
Eiji                         Kitahama Eiji
This is...
Rin                     Nanakura Rin
the beginning of...
Director - Script                         Iwata Tsuguto
~Beginning~
Our story.
Rin! You were so good in the short film!
You too, Senpai-san... What's wrong?
Senpai, Megu, and Kiri-chan are here.
Thank you for watching....
Seeing the finished product
made him really embarrassed.
He's so weird.
And this is really
Nanakura-senpai's boyfriend...?
The fact that there's record
of it on film is too much to bear...
Especially considering
the gap in our acting abilities!
Good point!
Obviously!
I think her acting
was different from usual!
I know, right?! Right?!
It really was!
So amazing!
You two get along, huh?
I'm not sure, but...
I think because this role
was based on my old self,
it might've been different than usual?
Well, that's my best guess!
You sure it's not because you were excited
about getting to work with Senpai-san again?
Dead
Um... is it possible
to get a copy of the film?
On DVD, if possible.
Oh, that's cool.
I'll ask Tsuu-chan about it.
Oh... I want one too.
Sure.
Awesome!
That's a relief... He's not that weird.
I am not.
Er... sorry.
I want one too.
Huh?! Uh, sure.
Nominated Films
Short
Films
About
Falling
In
Love
The Beginning of A Story
1,461,000 views
Holy moly...
Holy moly!
The Beginning of A Story
1,461,000 views
W-What happened, exactly?
The short film he entered
in the contest went viral!
People are talking about
how cute the female lead is!
Not only that,
but a talent agency contacted me through
the contest about wanting to meet you!
This is incredible! Way to go, Nanakura!
Uh... but this is so sudden...
It just means your efforts
are being acknowledged.
For now, congratulations.
It's just like I expected!
Right! This is good news!
Nanakura!
Don't forget about us once
you've ascended to stardom!
Th-That's... You're assuming an awful lot.
It's up to you to turn our flick
into something legendary!
Aw, come on, what are you saying?
I get the feeling it
might be legendary already.
Not compared to how legendary it will be!
Hey, did Nanakura-san seem odd to you?
You think so?
How about it, Eiji?
Huh... well... I'm not sure.
See ya!
Yeah.
See ya.
I forgot the most important thing...
Oh...
I'll make sure they get their copies.
Yeah, I appreciate it.
What's wrong?
Wait, you're worrying about your future, of course.
Yeah...
You're not going to accept the offer
from the talent agency, Nanakura-senpai?
I'm not sure.
I... I want to see more of your acting.
And being an actress
isn't something just anybody can do!
If you've been scouted,
that's all the more reason to...
You've got a point...
I always thought it would only be a dream,
but now that it seems
like it could be real...
I'm getting scared.
And I was finally going to be attending
the same school as Senpai...
How much longer do I have
to keep holding back?
But—
Whatever you end up doing,
you need to be the one to make the call.
That's cold.
This is a decision that will
determine your future, Rin.
You really want someone else to make it?
Graduation is coming soon, y'know.
That'll be 300,000 yen.
... just kidding.
Iwata
So cold!
Pseudo Harem
I wonder what Nanakura's gonna do...
Personally, I'd love her to continue acting.
What do you think, Eiji?
I'm the only one talking, here!
Well, I'm sure it's complicated for Eiji.
Well, what good is getting sulky
about it gonna do?
His only option is to accept her decision,
so the best thing to do either way
is to face her with a smile!
Y'know... I do realize that.
The thing is... it'd be one thing
if I was just waiting,
but I'm actually getting
in the way of her decision.
Yeah, you totally are.
Hey!
As a friend, shouldn't there
be something else you could say?
Listen up! If I was in your position?
I'd be absolutely inconsolable
and losing my damn mind!
So don't expect any consolation from me!
What happened to accepting
her decision with a smile...?
Our friendship will only really
shine once you've been abandoned.
Now, let's eat. My treat.
I appreciate it.
I wanna meet soon so we can talk
About the future
What's up?
Uh... sorry.
Go on without me.
Sure. See you.
Yeah.
I'm running out of time.
My dream, or the person I love...
And I still can't decide.
I feel like I'm stuck.
I wish things really were stuck.
Or that we could go back to that time...
This is where we first met.
President! Kitahama Eiji.
Meow!
There are too many things
I want to take pictures of!
Y'know, it's embarrassing
even for me, but...
I really wanna take in what
you're going to say, Rin.
Senpai... I think you're...
Since I was a first-year, I've always...
I've always loved you!
I love you too!
So fast...!
I didn't want to leave you hanging!
I know, but...
I didn't want you to wait even a second!
Too fast!
Rin!
When did you start liking me?
From the beginning, I'd say.
No way!
Well, I loved your acting
the first time I saw it.
I thought, "I wanna see her act more."
That makes me sound like just a fan...
But then you got
a role right away, remember?
And I wanted to watch your practice,
so I started dropping by the gym.
After that, the pseudo harem was born.
Right.
This is so hard...
Come on, why do I have to pick only one?
Someone is enjoying a bit of time travel.
Huh? Didn't you hear me?
H-Hey....
S-Senpai?
Were you watching? How long?
Well... from the start?
Oh, no! This is so embarrassing!
I mean, I knew you were having
trouble making up your mind.
And I don't blame you
for wanting to reminisce...
But now, let's head to the future!
Why are you here?
To... reminisce a little?
What the heck?
No, I just kinda wanted to
drop by, honestly.
I guess we were thinking the same thing.
I... want to stay with you, Senpai!
I don't care about acting
or my dreams or any of that!
I wanna be with you...
Okay.
But it's a little too soon to give up.
I figure it's up to me to make
that dream come true.
If I make my way up in the world,
I'll be able to work on projects
with you behind the scenes.
That way, you won't lose a single thing.
You've worked so hard for my sake...
and now it's my turn.
Don't worry!
I'll definitely catch up to you.
Senpai...
Thank you!
Sure.
Hey...
Tell me your dream, Senpai.
My dream?
Yeah. I want to make
your dream come true too.
Before I become an actress...
Then how about a smooch...
From Tsundere-chan!
A-Are you stupid?!
I can't do that sort of
thing out of the blue!
Y-You make the first move.
Smooch!
And then I want Spoiled-chan
to let me use her lap as a pillow...
Too bad! I'm gonna do it instead.
Wait, no!
I want to be the one who does it.
My dream...
Has to wait until I've caught up to you.
Man, it really is cold outside!
Let's get indoors.
Okay.
I'll be looking forward to it, then.
Yeah.
I'm sure we'll be together soon.
Hey, we're behind schedule
with the set dressing!
Kitahama-san!
This'll be your last time working
with us on-location, right?
Yep. Starting next week,
I've got a studio gig.
How do you move up so fast?
Well, I can't afford to wait around.
What makes you say that?
Oh, nothing.
Oh! Is it a girl?
You got a girl waiting, Kitahama-san?!
Knock it off! And hurry up
with those props already!
Sure, sure, you got it!
Unbelievable...
Hey! Quit slacking!
It's been a while, Ri—
Senpai!
Congratulations on your job
at the TV station!
Thanks.
Starting next week, we'll be
able to see each other there too.
I'm filming a drama there right now,
so I'll be coming by every day.
That's pretty awesome.
I'll get to see you every day.
I tend to get my co-stars
to fall for me, y'know...
You're gonna make me fall
into a depression, Imp-chan!
I've decided that it's my
career that I truly love.
Don't freeze me out, Cool-chan!
I finally managed to catch up to you.
Yeah.
I'm sorry it took so long.
It's okay. I still love you.
Rin...
I'm so glad you waited for me.
I wanna tell you... what I really
wanted to say, way back when.
It's about my dream,
the one only you can make come true.
I want us to get married!
Okay! I'll make it happen!
Rin! I love you the most ever!
Right!
When should the ceremony be?
Wait, we'll need to tell
our parents first, right?
Whoa, slow down a sec...
Oh, I had better let
people know I'm retiring!
You're leaving me behind!
Episode 12  The Beginning of a Story
I didn't expect we'd be doing this here...
All right, show's over! Everybody go home!
What are you talking about, Eiji?
You two are the stars today.
Well said, Club President!
Rin, you have to stay dressed
like that all day today!
I would really like to change!
I... I never thought
I'd get to see the day!
There, there...
Okay, but why are you crying?
Look at this huge crowd!
Seriously!
But it's kind of stuffy in here.
Senpai.
Yes?
Er... Nanakura-senpai.
There's something
I've been meaning to tell you...
I was really happy
that you continued acting.
Thank you.
You've been working hard too, Kiri-chan.
Yeah, I've seen you on TV lately.
Oh, no, I've still got a long way to go...
Congratulations on your marriage, Senpai.
Oh, you too, Kitahama-san.
Me too, huh?
Now, now...
This is...
Kinda...
Like "The Beginning of a Story."
What?
What's so funny?
Oh, nothing!
Man, you two really are made for each other.
Ain't we, though?
Isn't it great?